Hey everyone, today we are going to be
learning the old version of Lady Gaga's
Judas. This is the one from her original
music video. I did do the brand new
version, so if you want to learn that
one, go and check out that other video.
But, we're going to do the old school
Lady Gaga version. Let's start dancing.
All right, first eight count. If you
don't already know, I always have
chapters below, so you can fast forward
or rewind depending on how quickly you
learn. Very first thing I'm going to do
is tap my right forward and my right
hand goes up. And we're making fists or
you can do snaps. Okay, now we're going
to switch everything, arms and legs. Do
that two more times. Three.
Four. So, 1 2 3 4 is tapping forward
arms. 1
4. So, the arm that's up is always the
arm that's going forward. Five and six.
This arm is going to go back and open.
Five and six. So, you reach out
put it on your heart at the same time
your head drops down and bring it up.
Five and six. Okay, so let's go 1 2 3 4.
5 and 6. Make sure you have that
coordination. Now, even though I'm
tapped on this foot, I'm going to put
weight on it really quick to switch
forward 7 and close 8. So, I'm doing a
rock step on the right. Rock, step,
close. And when I close, that left hand
that was back closes into the heart as
well. Okay? So, that was harder than the
first four. So, I did my left foot's
forward. Five, head, arm goes in
head comes up six. Now, we're going to
do rock step seven and close eight. Yes,
again just that part. Five and six,
seven and eight. One more time. Five and
six, seven and eight. Yes? So, let's put
that full eight together. Here we go.
Five, six, seven, slow. One, two,
three, four,
five and six, seven and close eight.
Okay? That's your first eight count.
We're going to move on. If you need to
review it, go ahead and do that in the
chapters.
One and two, we're going to tap out with
our right. So, keep your weight in the
middle. One and two. Yeah? So, you
switch it out. So, you tap out.
Out. Yes? My hands go one and two. So,
it goes to the side, bring them in to
break down.
Yes? On three,
three.
Yes? So, kind of bring your head in
three. Close your foot. My head snaps
back up.
My foot comes in. Yes? So, one and two,
three.
So, it's just a tap on this left one cuz
now I step four, five.
Yes? So, do that again really slowly.
One and two,
three,
four, five.
We're going to go and six.
So, my head comes down again. Arms are
down.
Up on six,
seven and right hand, left hand.
Eight, I bring my shoulders, I bring my
hands down my body. Okay? Really slow.
One and two,
three,
four,
five and six,
seven and eight.
Yes? That's that full second eight
count. Let's do it just a little bit
faster. Five, six, seven, eight. One and
two, three, four, five and six, seven
and eight. Yeah? First and second eight
count put together. Here we go. Five,
six, seven, from the top. One, two,
three, four, five and six, seven and
close eight. One and two, three, four,
five and 6 7 and 8.
Not bad. Now, that entire two eight
counts repeat itself.
That's why this version is a lot easier
than the Coachella version, okay? So,
that entire thing you did, you'd go from
the you did 7 and 8 and you start over
1.
So, don't forget right foot goes
forward, right hand. So, let's just try
putting those first two eight counts
twice back-to-back from the top.
5 6 7, here we go.
1 2 3 4 5 and 6 7 and 8 1 and 2 3 4 5
and 6 7 and repeat. 1 2 3 4 5 and 6 7
and 8 1 and 2 3 4 5 and 6 7 and 8 Yes,
no, maybe so, kind of sort of.
From there this is even easier, okay?
So, we're just going to go side, side
circle, side. So, what did my feet do? I
just leaned right left chase with the
left, yes? I'm going to the right and
I'm chasing with my left foot to the
right foot. 1 2 3 and 4. Now, I do the
same thing the other way. Left foot
right foot, left, right, left. Yes? My
hands go swing to the right left circle
left right circle go.
So, that's technically your fifth eight
count. From here, this part's a little
goofy and I actually
don't know what it is cuz they zoom out,
but this is what people have done on
social media. You rock forward with the
right. Come back and then you're going
to kind of skip
to the other side. So, we go 1 2 and 3,
but now rock forward with that right
again.
4 5
Okay? Now, my arms go swing, swing,
swing
forward. Yeah? So, the second time I'm
rocking, my arms end up being opposite.
So, do that again.
1 2 and 3
4 5 6 7 8. Okay?
So, one more time just the feet. Rock,
step and switch. Rock, step, step and
switch. Rock. And the arms are just
always are alternating. They start back,
forward, back, forward, back, forward,
back, forward. So, it doesn't matter
what move you're doing, just that on
each beat you're switching. Yes? Slowly.
I know that's confusing. It does not
have to be perfect, you guys. So, from
here we did 1
2 and 3 4 5 6 and 7 8.
Yes?
Okay. Let's go all the way from the top.
Oh, and that repeats twice, too. So,
this thing 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 rock. 1 2 3 4 5
6 7 8.
Now, repeat. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 1 2 3 4 5 6
7 8. Yes? So, try it all the way from
the top very slowly. Here we go. 5 6 7
You got this. 1 2 3 4 5 and 6 7 and 8. 1
and 2. 3 4 5 and 6 7 and 8. Repeat. 2 3
4 5 and 6 7 and 8. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 and
side to side. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 rock step. 1
2 and 3 4 5 6 and 7 repeat. Side to
side. 3 4 5 6 7 rock step. 1 2 and 3 4 5
6 and 7 8.
And that is it you guys. Don't forget to
go try with music now. Thank you so much
for joining me today. Right here you do
it with music and it brings speed so go
ahead and practice it there as well. If
you have any suggestions I'm always open
for it so go ahead and drop it in the
comments below and we'll see you guys
next time. Bye.